[
  {
    "Question": "Hallo Ivan.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok Ivane." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "hallo - bok",
        "Word": "Hallo"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "",
        "Word": "Ivan."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hallo Marko.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok Marko." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "hallo - bok",
        "Word": "Hallo"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "",
        "Word": "Marko."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Morgen.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobro jutro." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Guten"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Morgen, der - jutro",
        "Word": "Morgen."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Morgen Klara.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobro jutro Klara." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Guten"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Morgen, der - jutro",
        "Word": "Morgen"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "",
        "Word": "Klara."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Tag.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobar dan." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Guten"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Tag, der - dan",
        "Word": "Tag."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Tag Julia.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobar dan Julia." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Guten"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Tag, der - dan",
        "Word": "Tag"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "",
        "Word": "Julia."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Abend.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobra večer." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Guten"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Abend, der - večer",
        "Word": "Abend."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gute Nacht.",
    "Answer": [ "Laku noć." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "gut – dobar",
        "Word": "Gute"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Nacht, die - noć",
        "Word": "Nacht."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Auf Wiedersehen.",
    "Answer": [ "Doviđenja." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "na/do",
        "Word": "Auf"
      },
      {
        "Explanation": "Wiedersehen, das – vidjeti se ponovo",
        "Word": "Wiedersehen"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tschüss.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok." ],
    "WordExplanations": [
      {
        "Explanation": "tschüss - bok",
        "Word": "Tschüss."
      }
    ]
  }
]